life insurance plan with guaranteed
returns
so listen till the end to gain more
knowledge about different life insurance
policies they make guaranteed payout
number one science smarter life Elite
with this plan the policy owner is
entitled to receive guaranteed cash
payout which is equal to eight percent
of the face amount
every other year is starting on the
sixth year but wait there's more the
policy owner or insured will receive
this guaranteed cash payout bill h100 or
habang
number two Sun accelerate this is an
endowment life insurance plan policy
owner will only pay eight years and
cover the shop for 20 years this
insurance plan also offers guaranteed
payout every other year starting on the
eighth year difference
and getting a plan which is science
smarter life Elite with the sun
accelerate if you are alive after 20
years you will receive the maturity
benefit equal to 102 of the face amount
well usually
plan people who only wanted temporary
life insurance coverage with money back
if not used meaning
for this plan
are you this type of person and speaking
of money back number three Sans tied up
this is the beginner friendly life
insurance plan in the market the policy
owners covered for 10 years and if he or
she survives
fifty percent of the total premiums made
will be returned among these three plans
that I just shared Sun startup is also
the most affordable plan
and to explain more about this tree
insurance plan the sun smarter and Sun
accelerate is actually more pricey
compared to other insurance plans for
these two plants the lowest premium is
around 35 to 50 000 per year
premium the policy owner will receive
guaranteed payout
for the last insurance plan which is Sun
startup the lowest premium is around 4
000 to 5 000 per year per dependian has
an actual profile the policy owner among
these three is
a comment section
example policy for your reference
[Music]
thank you